Yash Dave

D-504, The Oakwood, Road – C,
Vadodara, Gujarat, India - 391410

+91 - 97278 35873

mail2ypd@gmail.com

linkedin.com/in/amorpheuz in

github.com/amorpheuz 🕠

Frontend developer with experience in building webapps based on React.js and Pure HTML + CSS + JavaScript. Successfully completed 10 unique projects, each one having its own set of accomplished challenges. Backend development enthusiast with knowledge of .NET Core, PostgreSQL, MS-SQL, and MySQL. Love to experiment with new technologies, promote & help beginners getting comfortable with Open Source and an Occasional Blogger.

Skills

- React.js
- JavaScript
- HTML5 + CSS3
- Bootstrap

- C#, .NET Core
- Python
- PostgreSQL, MS-SQL, MongoDB, and Firebase
- Git
- VS Code
- Adobe Illustrator
- Adobe XD
- Linux, Windows, and WSL

Experience

2019/01 - 2019/05

Software Intern / NINtec Business Consulting LLP, Ahmedabad, Gujarat

- o Wrote code on .NET Core platform using Visual Studio, Entity Framework and MS-SQL.
- Built databases and table structures following ORM methodology for web applications.
- Evaluated project requirements & specifications and developed software application that surpassed mentor's expectations.

2018/05 - 2018/06

Software Intern / Potent Embedded Systems, Vadodara, Gujarat

- Created UML Diagrams for Stock Management application, further used by Software Developers to develop the project.
- Created modern website for subsidiary of the firm called TraxBee.
- Designed intuitive UI for Stock Management System.

Education

JUNE 2019 - CURRENT

Master of Science - Computer Applications / Symbiosis Institute of Computer Studies and Research, Pune

About to enter my final year for the Degree. Pursuing a specialization in the Data Science field.

Bachelor of Computer Applications / Navrachana University, Vadodara

Graduated with a CGPA of 9.5 / 10 (UGC 10-point system).

Projects and Open Source Contributions

DEV Community

 Contributing via opening <u>Issues</u> and <u>Pull Requests</u> related to Document Fixes/Updates, UI bugs and JavaScript Linting.

Onion Rooting

- A DApp which makes used of Ethereum smart contracts which aims to solve the problem of crop/produce hoarding by intermediaries. Link to demo: <u>The Onion Rooting</u>
- Technology Stack: React.js, Solidity, web3.js and Bootstrap.

• The Intelligent Donor

- A webapp aimed as a solution for people in urgent need of finding Blood Donors.
- Technology Stack: Bootstrap, Firebase and JavaScript.

Auto Issue Labeler

- o A console-based app that helps automatically classify a GitHub issue and label them.
- Technology Stack: C#, .NET Core and ML.NET

Mozilla India

 Contributed via opening <u>Issues</u> and <u>Pull Requests</u> related to an older version of <u>site</u> which was based on Pure HTML, CSS, and JS along with using the framework Bulma.

Mozilla Gujarat

 Contributing via opening <u>Issues</u>, having mentoring sessions on best practices with the contributors and reviewing Pull Requests.

Activities and Accomplishments

- Current Vice-Chair of SICSR ACM Student Chapter.
- Enthusiastic Mozillian and actively participating with <u>Mozilla Gujarat</u>, <u>Mozilla Pune</u>, and <u>Mozilla</u> India.
- Moderator and avid member of Facebook Developer Circle: Pune.
- Recipient of Developer Circle Training Courses Scholarship (Track 1) for Web Development courses under OpenClassrooms which included:
 - o <u>Build web apps with ReactJS</u>, <u>Learn Programming with JavaScript</u> and <u>Create Web Page Layouts</u> with CSS.
- Delivered talks about Front-end concepts, React.js and Best Programming practices on multiple occasions.
- Successfully organized 4th National ACM-W Hackathon as part of the Technical Team overseeing hackers compete from all-over India.
- Runner-up Symtaxify Hackathon, 2019.
- Vice-Chair and Publisher of Computers@NUV from June 2017 October 2018.
- Successfully organized TechNUVate, college Techfest, for 2017 & 2018 as part of the Core Organizing Team with each seeing 200+ attendees.
- Recipient of M.V.P. Local Hack Day Vadodara, 2018.